Guide to the Gay and Lesbian Pulp Fiction Collection 1955-1988 MSS 116 MSS.116
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Third Accretion
  - Award Books A554X. Keene, Hadrian: Noon and Night. (Universal Publishing), 1969 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Badboy Adult Fiction. Anonymous: Bad Boy Fantasies. (Badboy), 1992 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Ballantine Books S389K. Kronhausen, Dr. Phyllis and Eberhard: Sex Histories of American College Men. (Ballantine), 1960 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Barclay House Homophile Fiction 7054. Maggie, John: The Honey Horn. (Barclay), 1969 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Barclay House Psycho-Sex Study 7106. Cook, Bill: Gay Teen Boys. (Barclay), 1970 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Beacon Signal 509F. Carr, Jay: Unnatural Wife. (Universal Publishing), 1962 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Beacon Signal 649F. Smith, Artemis: The Third Sex. (Universal Publishing), 1959 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Beacon Signal B663X. Addams, Kay: Queer Patterns. (Universal Publishing), 1959 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Bee-Line Books 328N. Seran, Val: Two-Way Girls. (Bee-Line), 1968 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Bee-Line Books 287S. Seran, Val: Branded Women. (Bee-Line), 1967 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Black Knight Classics. Anonymous: Adventures of Edward Buddy. (Guild Press), 1969 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Blue Boy Library 80040. Sanderson, Loren: Eden Reconsidered. (Blue Boy), 1977 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Blue Boy Library 80053. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: The Executioner. (Blue Boy), 1977 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Blue Boy Library 80076. Crown, Morris: Go-Go Boy. (Blue Boy), 1977 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Blue Boy Library 80077. Sanderson, Loren: Queen of the Club. (Blue Boy), 1977 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Boy Nymphet. Llewellyn, Terry. (w.l), undated (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Boudoir Classics. Ord, Sam: Summer Stock Sex Theatre. (K.S. Publishing), 1964 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Brandon House 959. Blake, Roger: The Homosexual Explosion. (Brandon House), 1966 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Brandon House 970. Robie, M.D: Sex Histories. (Brandon House), 1966 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Brandon House #3063. Gorman, Meredith: Homo Playboy. (Brandon House), 1969 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061162 9
  - Brandon House #3065. Michaels, Phil: The Naive Homosexual. (Brandon House), 1969 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Brandon House #6023. Kaye, H.R: The Perverted Triangle. (Brandon House), 1968 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Brandon House #6051. Paul, Harry: My Boy My Lover. (Brandon House), 1969 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Cameo Novel 8004. Evans, Gene: Homo Hunt. (Cameo), 1969 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Centaur Publications. Anonymous: Train Station Sex. (Centaur), 1970 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Century Books 5. Bradley, Matt: Queer Street U.S.A.. (Century), 1965 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Classic Publications 865. Collins, Jon: The Homosexual Profile. (Classic), 1968 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Club Series 110. Kell, C: The Young Hustlers. (Star Distributors), 1973 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Collectors' Publication. Durrell, Lawrence: The Black Box. (Collectors'), 1967 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Continental Classics 155. Pedersen, Axel: Intimate Seductions. (Continental), 1968 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Continental Classic 242. Derwent, Justin: Flaming Faggot. (Continental), 1969 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Crest Book 187. Taylor, Valerie: Whisper Their Love. (Crest), 1957 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Curtis Books 7271. Carpenter, Carleton: Games Murderers Play. (Curtis Books), 1973 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Dragon Edition 111. Aldon, Rick: Perverted Performers. (Dragon), 1965 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Eagle Books 84. Mallet-Joris, Francoise: The Loving and the Daring. (Popular Library), 1957 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Europa Novel 106. Lopez, Felipe: Queer Pleasure. (Europa), 1968 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Fabian Original Novel 103. Shane, Mark: The Lady Was A Man. (Fabian), 1955 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - France F32. Anonymous: Hollywood Lesbian. (International Publications), 1963 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - French Line 3. Coley, Carl: The Scarlet Lantern. (Publishes' Export Company), 1966 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - French Line 27. Mayzk, R.G: Queens Town Court. (P.E.C), undated (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - French Line 46. Austin, Drew: Queer Pen. (P.E.C.), 1968 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - French Line 59. Geis, Alex: The Prick of the Picador. (P.E.C.), 1969 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - French Line 90. Royce, Roger: Gay Gang Up. (P.E.C.), 1970 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - French Line 101. Lasher, Bill: Making It. (P.E.C.), 1971 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Frenchy's Gay Line 19. Vanden, Dirk: All Or Nothing. (F.G.L.), 1970 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061199 1
  - Golden Boy Books 120. Michaels, Ward: Star Struck. (Arena Publications), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Gold Medal KL346. Packers, Vin: The Evil Friendship. (Fawcett Publications), 1958 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Goldstripe Gay Series 108. McKay, Travis: Love Mouth. (Eros Publishing), 1974 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Grand Prix Classics. Breaker, Dan: Virgin Boy. (w.l), undated (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Greenleaf Classic 110. Bortner, Jadkle: The Good Fairy. (Greenleaf), 1969 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Greenleaf Classic 116. Weeks, Barry: Cock-Of-the-Walk. (Greenleaf), 1969 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Greenleaf Classic 119. Barton, Lee: Tricks Hot, Tricks Cold. (Greenleaf), 1969 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Greenleaf Classic 131. Francis, Julian: Bunny Bitch. (Greenleaf), 1969 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Greenleaf Classic 153. Lambert, William J: Demon's Stalk. (Greenleaf), 1970 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Greenleaf Classic 307. Armory, Richard: Fruit Of the Loon. (Greenleaf), 1968 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Greenleaf Classic 409. Thomas, Aaron: Cockshy. (Greenleaf), 1973 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Hourglass Library 1007. Rathermann, Alfredo: Orgy 1970.. (Oligarch Publishing) (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Imperial Book 730. Dorian, Lee: The Young Homosexual. (L.S. Publishing), 1965 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Intimate Edition 709. Bradley, Matt: Faggots to Burn. (Art Enterprises), 1962 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Intimate Edition 727. Nemec, John: Is She A Dyke. (Art Enterprises), 1963 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Lancer Books 72-789. Janifer, Lawrence: You Sane Men. (Lancer), 1965 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Klaf, Franklin: Satyriasis, A Study of Male Nymphomania. (Lancer), 1966 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Late-Hour Library 769. Gamlin, Douglas: Homosexual Incest. (Phenix Publishers), 1968 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Mayfair House Classic 1046. Brink, Alex: Gay Relations. (N.P.), Inc: 1970 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Midwood 508M-195-146. St. Clair, Roger: Caged. (Midwood Enterprises), 1971 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Monkey Publications, Inc. Evans, Jack: The Gay Ship Lollipop. (Monkey), 1969 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Monkey Publications, Inc. Travis, Vic: The Salesman and the Hitchhiker. (Monkey), 1969 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Numbers Paperback Library 10013. Moritzen, Nils: I Am Curious [Gay]. (Numbers), 1978 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Original Home Library 7. Richards, Paul: Big Daddy's Boy. (101 Enterprises), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061198 3
  - Original Home Library 12. Ricco, Mario: Little Boy Gay. (101 Enterprises), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Original Home Library 14. Roberts, Pudge: Dormitory Mates. (101 Enterprises), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Original Home Library 16. Coolen, Carl: School For Young Slave Boys. (101 Enterprises), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Original Home Library 20. Rice, Walter: Balcony Bunnies. (101 Enterprises), 1967 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Original Home Library 32. Coolen, Carl: Ballet For Boys. (101 Enterprises), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Original Home Library 36. Carter, Floyd: Forbidden Fruit. (101 Enterprises), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Pad Library 556. Sharon, Michael: A Half World. (Pad Library), 1967 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Paramount Publishers SL515. Danbury, Dylan: He's Gay and Married. (Paramount), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Parisian Press 214. Graves, John: Campus Gang Bang. (Parisian Press), 1972 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - P.E.C-Human Experience Series 101. Corley, Carl: Faces In Secret. (P.E.C.), 1967 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - P.E.C.-Human Experience Series 102. Drew, Dennis: Like Father Like Son. (P.E.C.), 1967 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Pendulum 88. James, Adrian: I, Homosexual. (Pendulum), 1968 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Pleasure Reader 236. Sawyers, Rod: The Birds and the Bees. (Pleasure Reader), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Pleasure Reader 239. Falkon, Felix Lance: Hitchhiked and Other Stories. (Pleasure Reader), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Pleasure Reader 240. Edmunds, E.B: Unknown To the Crowd. (Phenix Publishers), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Pleasure Reader 242. Dean, Douglas: Madder Music, Stronger Wine. (Phenix), 1969 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Pleasure Reader 263. Lamarr, Barry: Gay Like Me. (Phenix Publishers), 1970 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Pleasure Reader 264. Falkon, Felix Lance: Castration Castle. (Phenix Publishers), 1970 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Pleasure Reader 273. Peale, Billy: Coming Out.. .West. (Phenix Publishers), 1970 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Pleasure Reader 280. Hawkes, H.C: The Long Gay Line. (Phenix Publishers), 1970 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Pleasure Reader 302. Fair, Alan: The New Boy. (Phenix Publishers), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Pleasure Reader 303. Wayne, W.W: Snowbound In Sodom. (Greenleaf Classics), 1971 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Pleasure Reader 307. Townsend, Larry: Beware Of the God Who Smiles. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061163 7
  - Pleasure Reader 314. Peale, Billy: The Seeds of Spring. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Pleasure Reader 316. Spar, Jack: Just Friends. (Greenleaf Classics), 1971 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Pleasure Reader 332. St. Lorenz, Jimmy: Prison Isle. (Greenleaf Classics), 1971 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Pleasure Reader 337. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: Strangers Can See You In My Face. (Greenleaf), 1971 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Pleasure Reader 352. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: Something In the Blood. (Greenleaf), 1972 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Pleasure Reader 373. Raborg, Frederick: Dude On Second Avenue. (Greenleaf), 1972 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Pleasure Reader 376. Vanden, Dirk: Who Killed Queen Tom. (Greenleaf), 1972 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Pleasure Reader 383. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: Spin The Boy Down. (Greenleaf), 1972 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Pleasure Reader 395. Sutherland, John: Paul's Coming Out. (Greenleaf Classics), 1972 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Popular Library Fiction. Delligan, William: Fire Island Pines. (Popular Library), 1977 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Private Editions Novel 375. Bright, Lynwood: The Men Between. (Private Editions), 1966 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Pyramid Books 32. Kent, Nial: The Divided Path. (Greenberg), 1949 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Pyramid Books F-752. Royer, Louis-Charles: The Flesh. (Pyramid Books), 1962 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Pyramid Books R-686. Choisy, Maryse: A Month Among the Men. (Pyramid), 1962 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Pyramid Books R-1220. Lacy, Ed: Harlem Underground. (Pyramid), 1965 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Regency 1021. Dunn, Mark: Gay Sadist. (Regency), 1970 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Roadhouse Classics 133. Proferes, JJ: Gay Company-69th Battalion. (Guild Press), 1972 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Scan Book 114. Brent, Marvin: Male Sex For Sale. (Central Sales), 1969 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Softcover Library B899X. Travis, Ben: The Strange Ones. (Softcover Library), 1959 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Spartan Classic 111. Kaye, H.R.: Green and Tender. (GX Inc.), 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061197 5
  - Spartan Classic 114. Kaye, H.R.: Gay Obsession. (GX Inc.), 1973 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Spartan Classic 116. Russell, Thomas: The Edge of Sin. (GX Inc.), 1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Taurus Publications 224. Paul, Harry: Love. (Taurus), 1969 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Timely Books. Barnes, Chuck: Revenge. (Timely Books), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Timely Books. Hale, E.M: Young Boy Hard. (Timely Books), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Tower 45-168. Greene, Jay: Rough Trade. (Tower), 1969 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Trojan Classic 202. Garfield, Dick: Tearoom Castles. (GX), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Trojan Classic 203. Rogers, Lance: Searchlight Insight. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Trojan Classic 218. Richard Manbow and Lyn Pedersen: Do My Thing. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Trojan Classic 226. Cocker, Charles: Weak End. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Trojan Classic 233. Drury, Sean: Cops and Bobbers. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Trojan Classics 242. Roberts, Lance: A Hand In the Bush. (GX Inc.), undated (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Traveler's Companion 512. Vanden, Dirk: All Is Well. (Traveler's Companion), 1971 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Twi-World Publications 20. Anonymous: Chosen Society. (Twi-World ), 1968 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Twilight Classics 102. Faulk, Guy: It's A Gay, Gay World. (Guild Press), 1968 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Twilight Classics 104. Randolph, Peter: Beat It, Kid. (Guild Press), 1968 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Twilight Classics 115. Proferes, James J: Prison Punk. (Guild Press), 1969 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Twilight Classics 121. Proferes, James J: Any Man Is Fair Game. (Guild Press), 1969 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Two: Two Stories of Two Boys. Jason Forbes. (w.l), 1969 (Box 44, Folder 20)